https://solutionsforaccounting.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Search for:
MENUMENUNewslettersBlogTestimonialsCase StudiesEventsCareersOur TeamAbout usAwards and AccreditationsContact UsSolutions SupportSupportTeamViewer Remote SupportTeamViewer MeetingsFileDropSelf ServiceSoftware SupportSage Accounting SupportSage CRM SupportAct! CRM SupportSalesforce SupportNot sure what you’re looking for?Speak to our teamServicesServicesSolutions SupportSolutions TrainingReport Writing & DesignerCustomisationNot sure what you’re looking for?Speak to our teamAddonsAddonsBusiness Automation SoftwareCredit Control SoftwareExpense Management SoftwarePayment Processing SoftwareManufacturing Management SoftwareWarehouse Management SoftwareRetail Management SoftwareSolutions AdditionsForecasting SoftwareDocument Management SoftwareConstruction Management SoftwarePayroll SoftwareService Management SoftwareSage DashboardsShipping SoftwareHosted Desktop SoftwareBy IndustryBy IndustryManufacturingNot for ProfitSubscription & SaaSWholesale and DistributionProfessional ServicesRetailIndependent Schools accounting softwareConstructionNot sure what you’re looking for?Speak to our teamSalesforceSalesforce SoftwareSalesforce CRMExtrasSalesforce SupportSalesforce TrainingNot sure what you’re looking for?Speak to our teamAct!Act! SoftwareAct! CRMExtrasAct! Marketing AutomationAct! MobileAct! CRM SupportAct! CRM TrainingNot sure what you’re looking for?Speak to our teamSageSage SoftwareSage 50Sage 200Sage IntacctSage CRMView All Sage SoftwareExtrasSolutions Additions for Sage 50Solutions Additions for Sage 200Sage Accounting SupportSage CRM SupportSage TrainingSage CRM TrainingNot sure what you’re looking for?Speak to our team
Home>Privacy Policy>
Privacy PolicyColumn 2Solutions for Accounting and CRM (“We”) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it.For the purpose of the General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR), the data controller is Solutions for Accounting Limited (Trading as Solutions for Accounting and CRM) of Sherwood House, 7 Gregory Boulevard. Nottingham, NG7 6LB.Information we may collect from youWe may collect and process the following data about you:Information that you provide by filling in forms on our site www.solutionsforaccounting.co.uk . This includes any information provided at the time of registering to use our site, subscribing to our service, purchasing software modules from our site or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our site.If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.We may also ask you to complete surveys that we use for research purposes, although you do not have to respond to them.Details of transactions you carry out through our site and of the fulfilment of your orders.Details of your visits to our site including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, whether this is required for our own billing purposes or otherwise and the resources that you access.whether you subscribe to our newsletter and or whether you access the same.IP addresses and cookiesWe may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration. This is statistical data about our users’ browsing actions and patterns, and does not identify any individual.For the same reason, we may obtain information about your general internet usage by using a cookie file which is stored on the hard drive of your computer. Cookies contain information that is transferred to your computer’s hard drive. They help us to improve our site and to deliver a better and more personalised service.Cookies are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site. At present the site does not use cookies.Where we store your personal dataThe data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. Such staff may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.Any payment transactions will be processed by a third party service provider. Our partner for the processing of payments for purchases that you make from our site is SagePay (formerly known as Protx) and use of SagePay will be subject to the terms and conditions of SagePay in force from time to time and will be subject to such encryption and security protocols as they may from time to time operate.Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.Uses made of the informationWe use information held about you in the following ways:To ensure that content from our site is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.To allow you to participate in interactive features of our service, when you choose to do so.To notify you about changes to our service.We may also use your data, or permit selected third parties to use your data, to provide you with information about goods and services which may be of interest to you and we or they may contact you about these by post, telephone or email.If you are an existing customer, we will only contact you by electronic means (e-mail or SMS) with information about goods and services similar to those which were the subject of a previous sale or in relation to new products that we feel may be of interest to you based on your previous purchases with us.If you are a new customer, and where we permit selected third parties to use your data, we (or they) will contact you by electronic means only if you have consented to this.Disclosure of your informationWe may disclose your personal information to a third party(i) If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements.(ii) To protect the rights, property, or safety of Solutions for Accounting Ltd, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purpose of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.Your rightsYou have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will inform you (before collecting your data) if we would like to use your data for such purposes or if we might intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes, and seek your permission before doing so. You can also advises us of any change to your stated preferences at any time by contacting us at Solutions for Accounting Ltd, Sherwood House, 7 Gregory Boulevard, Nottingham NG7 6LB.Further to this, you have the right to obtain the erasure of your personal data from our systems, providing that we are not under any duty or legal obligation to preserve that data (in whole or in part). You may request that we remove your personal data from our systems by contacting us at Solutions for Accounting Ltd, Sherwood House, 7 Gregory Boulevard, Nottingham NG7 6LB.Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.Access to informationThe General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR) give you the right to access personal information that we hold about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the regulations by contacting us at Solutions for Accounting Ltd, Sherwood House, 7 Gregory Boulevard, Nottingham NG7 6LB.Please refer also to our GDPR Statement of Compliance which describes what actions the company has taken to ensure the protection of your rights. The statement also explains the treatment of personal data on a wider basis (beyond the privacy policy which is associated with our website).Changes to our privacy policyAny changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail.ContactQuestions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to enquiries@solutionsforaccounting.co.uk.To find out how our software experts can help give you complete control over your business, call us today on 0115 840 5075 or email enquiries@solutionscloud.ukSpeak to Our TeamGet in touch…Call us on 0115 840 5075Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberBriefly explain the nature of your enquirye.g. "I'd like to discuss setting up Sage200 with somebody"0 / 180Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *YesNoGDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send
Close this module Arrange a Free DemoName *Your Company *Email Address *Phone Number *Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send your request
Close this module Guide DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the guide.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Download guide
Close this module Request a bespoke quote Please fill out the following form and we will get in contact with you with your Salesforce quote.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberNumber of users *Additional CommentsDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *YesNoGDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Get your bespoke quote
Close this module Comparison Guide DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we will send you a link to the support comparison guide.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Download guide
Close this module Webinar DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we will send you a link to the webinar.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Go to webinar
Close this module Enquiry FormName *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberBriefly explain the nature of your enquirye.g. "I'd like to discuss setting up Sage200 with somebody"0 / 180Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send
Close this module Case Study DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to our case study.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Download Case Study
Close this module Webinar DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we will send you a link to the webinar.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Go to webinar
Close this module Webinar LinkPlease fill out the following form and we will send you a link to the webinar.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Go to webinar
Close this module Request a CallbackPlease fill out the following form and a member of our team will get in touch to arrange a callback at a time to suit you.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone Number *Briefly explain the nature of your enquirye.g. "I'd like to discuss setting up Sage200 with somebody"0 / 180Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send
Close this module Arrange a Free DemoName *Your Company *Email Address *Phone Number *Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send your request
Close this module Arrange a Free Sage 50 DemoName *Your Company *Email Address *Phone Number *Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send your request
Close this module Arrange a Free Sage CRM DemoName *Your Company *Email Address *Phone Number *Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send your request
Close this module Arrange a Free DemoName *Your Company *Email Address *Phone Number *Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send your request
Close this module Arrange a Free DemoName *Your Company *Email Address *Phone Number *Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send your request
Close this module Brochure DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the brochure.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Download Brochure
Close this module Request a bespoke quote Please fill out the following form and we will get in contact with you with your Sage 200 quote.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberNumber of users *Additional CommentsDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *YesNoGDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Get your bespoke quote
Close this module Leaflet DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the leaflet.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Leaflet
Close this module Brochure DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the brochure.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Brochure
Close this module Guide DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the guide.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Guide
Close this module Take the TourPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the tour.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send Message
Close this module Request a bespoke quote Please fill out the following form and we will get in contact with you with your Sage Intacct quote.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberNumber of business users *Number of full users *Number of additional entities/businesses Additional modules needed *Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *YesNoGDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Get your bespoke quote
Close this module Brochure DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the brochure.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send Message
Close this module View webinarPlease fill out the following form and we will send you a link to the webinar.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Go to webinar
Close this module Brochure DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the brochure.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Download brochure
Close this module Request a bespoke quote Please fill out the following form and we will get in contact with you with your Sage Intacct quote.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberNumber of business users *Number of full users *Number of additional entities/businesses Additional modules needed *Don't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *YesNoGDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Get your bespoke quote
Close this module Datasheet DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the datasheet.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Download datasheet
Close this module Datasheet DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we will send you a link to the datasheet.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Download datasheet
Close this module Datasheet DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the datasheet.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Datasheet
Close this module Datasheet DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the datasheet.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Datasheet
Close this module Take the TourPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the tour.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Send Message
Close this module Webinar LinkPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the webinar.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Webinar
Close this module Request a bespoke quote Please fill out the following form and we will get in contact with you with your Salesforce quote.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberNumber of users *Additional CommentsDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *YesNoGDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Get your bespoke quote
Close this module Watch webinar nowPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the webinar.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Watch webinar
Close this module Datasheet DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the datasheet.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Webinar
Close this module Datasheet DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the datasheet.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Webinar
Close this module Datasheet DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we'll send you a link to the datasheet.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.View Webinar
Close this module Brochure DownloadPlease fill out the following form and we will send you a link to the brochure.Name *Your Company *Email Address *Phone NumberDon't miss out! Make sure you're the first to know all about the latest updates, advanced features and much more by selecting yes. You won't regret it. *GDPR Approval *Yes, I agree with your privacy policy and the terms and conditions.Brochure downloadThis website uses cookies to improve your experience. We'll assume you're ok with this, but you can opt-out if you wish. Cookie settingsACCEPTPrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Read Our Privacy Policy
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Any cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
Get in Touch0115 840 5075 or send us an email Request a Callback
